and now it's time for new Netflix
categories we need
them I'm sure you guys as you are
netflixing have noticed that uh there
are bizarrely specific categories in
Netflix like dark Canadian Thrillers or
visually striking fatherson
movies so comedians in 60 seconds I want
you to buzz in with as many new Netflix
categories as you can uh for each one
that makes us laugh 250 points Ready set
go Ricky lyol Sundance movies about AIDS
I that might already be one but I'll
give you points Jonah Ray movies that
don't hold
up that would be awesome category most
of them points yes Ricky Kier nightly
sobs in a
corset that's got to be like 14 right
there that keep you occupi for a week
points Kyle dunigan Seth Rogan movies
not made by Jed AO
Point yes Jonah Ray Gandhi chick
flicks
Ricky when Jeremy Piven was still bald
oh points yeah like anything before like
98 yeah singles yes threee legal Olen
twin wait will you please say that as
Craig pre-legal entrance yes yes
than music document oh don't do it do it
music documentary is about bands you've
never heard of that never made it yes
buds Ricky um movies where white women
solve racial
issues points uh Jonah uh movies Nick
Cage made because he's in debt
yes